// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " When dealing with identifiers is python case sensitive?",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "Machine independent",
      "In some cases"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What will the format() function return?",
    answer: "String",
    options: [
      "Int",
      "Float",
      "Char",
      "String"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In python programming,what is the maximum possible length of an identifier?",
    answer : "None of these",
    options: [
      "32",
      "64",
      "128",
      "None of these"
      ]
      
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Python was released in?",
    answer: "February 1991",
    options: [
      "February 1991",
      "December 1991",
      "December 1989",
      "February 1989"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Python is:",
    answer: "Interpreted Language",
    options: [
      "Interpreted Language",
      "Compiled Language",
      "Binary Language",
      "Static Language"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Python is a ______ typed language:",
     answer: "Strongly and Dynamically",
     options: [
       "Strongly and Dynamically",
       "Weak and Dynamic",
       "Strong and Static",
       "Weak and Static"
     ]
   },
    {
     numb: 7,
     question: "Which of the following is not an implementation of python?",
     answer: "FPython",
     options: [
       "Iron Python",
       "CPython",
       "FPython",
       "Stackless Python"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "How character data type is specified in Python",
     answer: "No Character data type in python",
     options: [
       "No Character data type in python",
       "Character",
       "char",
       "char()"
     ]
   },
  {
     numb: 9,
     question: "Which of the following is not a Data-type in python?",
     answer: "enumerate",
     options: [
       "String",
       "Integer",
       "bool",
       "enumerate"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Predict the output of the python code:  a=4.5  b=2  print(a//b)",
     answer: "2.0",
     options: [
       "2.0",
       "2",
       "2.25",
       "2.3"
     ]
   },
];